I tried to make a million dollars in 7
days trading and I failed miserably. And
whether you believe it or not or you
like me or not, I have made millions of
dollars in the markets. And I want to
make something extremely [music]
clear. Whether you think I'm a demo
trader or a fake trader or you just
don't believe in trading as a whole,
it's okay because I I could actually be
the biggest demo trader and not even a
actual person that executes [music]
trades because there is not tens, not
hundreds, not thousands, there's tens of
thousands of people [music] that execute
these trades that I am predicting every
single week completely for free. Like
don't take my word for it, you can
literally see it right here. I'm
literally just sharing on social media.
I'm entering this trade, you can take it
if you want or you don't if you don't
have to. Where only people like to focus
on my wins and call [music] it fake
because it's a lot of money, I get it.
It might seem unrealistic, but just 4
weeks ago I lost $120,000 in one single
trade. I then lost $200,000 on a second
week where I was on a 2-week losing
streak. Then I made it back where I made
$350,000 and I literally recorded all of
these trades live. You guys can go check
it out on this YouTube channel. [music]
But this last week I made a $734,000
in one single week. And I think more
than 15,000 people executed the exact
same trade that I took. Now, if you want
to call my trades demo, you want to call
my trades fake, that's fine. But you
can't call 15,000 people that they
executed and made money on this trade
fake because they're happy about it and
they want me to keep doing it. And guess
what? I will. So, let me break down how
I attempted to make a million dollars
while I was trading in Dubai
and almost failed. And this
record-breaking week was no coincidence.
The week prior to me actually breaking
my record and having this nearly
million-dollar trade, I did a recap
video for the YouTube video and for my
community of how the weekly candlesticks
and how the market closed. And as I'm
seeing the weekly candlestick close, the
daily candlestick closed, I'm realizing,
holy [__] this market [music] is
actually setting up the perfect trade
for the following week. So, the week
prior to me having this million-dollar
trade nearly, I didn't take a trade
because the market was consolidating for
the majority of the week and there
wasn't any great opportunity. For next
week I see some crazy market
opportunities going down. When it comes
to continuation in this trade setup. But
that consolidation was actually creating
the perfect setup for the following
week. I'm like, "Oh, can this not be a
better perfect storm?" Because that
actual following next week, I have to
head to Dubai because there's a big
Forex Expo. I got invited by a couple
big businesses out there to be a speaker
and I said, "Okay, you know what? I'm
going to go ahead and go to Dubai." As
soon as I get to Dubai, I realize that
it's actually even more of a perfect
storm simply because of the time zone. I
wake up at 8:00 in the morning, that is
pre-London session and I'm actually
awake the whole entire day and I'm able
to watch my trade and not have to be
fighting my sleep how I do here on
Eastern time zone. And that's where I
realized that this is going to be a
great week. And let me tell you
something, even if you get business
class from Miami to Dubai with Emirates,
lay down, best service, amazing,
this 15-hour flight is still [__]
brutal.
And I've done this 15-hour flight
multiple times and I know how brutal it
can be. And I wanted to come prepared
this time around. I actually wanted to
properly get some sleep on it so when I
get to Dubai, I'm like almost connected
in the time zone so I'm not jet-lagged.
For the first time ever, my team that
I'm going with to Dubai convinced me to
take melatonin. I've never taken
melatonin in my life. So, I decided to
double down and take two of these
melatonin shots at the airport, right?
Not not not knowing how strong it is.
I'm falling asleep walking onto the
plane. Like I'm literally walking into
the plane falling asleep. Get into the
lay down, I lay down and what I think is
20 minutes later, I get woken up by the
by the stewardess and she says, "Hey, uh
sir, can you please lift up your seat?
Uh we're landing."
What do you mean we're landing? So, I
get yeah, uh sir, we're in Dubai.
I knocked out the whole 15-hour flight.
And if that wasn't enough, when we got
to the hotel, I fell asleep another 8
hours.
Safe to say, I'm never in my life again
taking melatonin and I was very well
recovered, ready to trade this upcoming
week. So, after we wake up the next day
after pretty much sleeping 24, 25, 26
hours, the first thing I needed to do in
Dubai is get a car. And I don't want to
be like another one of these gurus
driving around in a Lambo, Ferrari,
McLaren. Like we already have that in
Miami and we don't want to just come off
the wrong way in Dubai. We went to a uh
Ahmed, really cool guy out there in
Miami, rented us a 7 Series. And we
thought it was a bright idea the first
thing to do was go to the desert.
Straight out of the rental office, go
straight into the desert and go be
iconic and find some camels.
Yeah, I thought I was in a G Wagon for
whatever reason with a 4x4 and we got
stuck.
That was not fun. You mix
a black car
with 110° weather and sand, that's a
perfect equation for a [__] Yo, we
just saw a whole pack of camels, bro.
[__] BRO.
IT'S STUCK, BRO. IT'S EXACTLY what I
[__] said, dude.
Whatever, we'll just go get the camel
and we'll figure this [__] out later.
>> [music]
[music]
>> So, after a humbling experience in the
desert of Dubai, wake up the next day
around 8:00 in the morning and I do my
market analysis right around 8:30, 8:40
in the morning, which is actually 1:00
in the morning Eastern Standard Time,
right? So, this is Friday morning Dubai
time, 8:00 a.m. and it's 1:00 a.m.
Friday night or Friday morning
technically. And I don't ever take
trades after London session on Thursday
[music] or Thursday New York session.
So, we are literally in the last session
of the week, right? So, the market
probably has another 8 hours before the
last volume ends and I don't like taking
trades this close into the closure of
the week simply because either one,
there's going to be no volatility in the
market or simply the cost to take the
trade is going to be too high. So,
EUR/USD gave me the perfect head and
shoulders, gave me the perfect break of
the neckline, everything that I wanted
to enter the trade. But I said, "Okay,
you know what? It's okay that this trade
is doing this here because this is
actually setting up the perfect trade
for the following week." So, that's
where I realized that the next week was
actually going to be perfect. This is
where everything literally came
together. So, I know EUR/USD was going
to give me the perfect trade to the
downside after the retest of the head
and shoulders. I know GBP/CHF was going
to be a massive countertrend trade. And
then we had AUD/USD, which is going to
give me a what I thought was going to be
a perfect buy. And funny enough, I was
pretty much trading [music]
against each other. I was going to sell
EUR/USD, which I'm betting on a strong
dollar, and then AUD/USD, I'm buying,
which I'm betting on a weak dollar. Now,
I do this pretty often because I like to
see the difference [music] in the USD
and whichever one gives me the cleanest
and the best confirmation is typically
what ends up happening. And that's
exactly what happened on that following
week. And at that very moment, I already
knew that those were going to be my top
three markets for the week. Even though
we had a clean USD/CHF, [music]
GBP/AUD, GBP/USD and a couple of other
markets that I break down,
I but I'd say about two out of all those
four markets actually had the move, but
I wasn't really fully prioritizing them
how I did with the other ones that were
my top three for the [music] week. I
always like to have seven, eight markets
for the week and I like to pick my top
two or three which are going to have the
highest probability trade setup, which
means I have the lowest risk.
>> All right, boys.
>> [laughter]
>> [__] finally. Fast forward 3 days
later, we are
we're back. We're officially here in
Dubai. I don't know if you guys can tell
based off of yesterday's clips or I
don't know, when I was recording my
computer was just completely bugging
out. Not sure if it was because of the
VPNs or because of the Wi-Fis, but boys,
we are in Dubai as we currently speak.
Burj Khalifa view.
The best view.
I don't know, I'm just saying what all
the locals say.
Um this is what matters right here,
right? We we've been trying to trade
this whole entire week and the time
zones are honestly ridiculous. So, right
now, it is currently
8:40 in the morning Dubai time and it is
currently 1:00 in the morning Miami
time.
It's Friday?
Wait, what?
Wait, if it's 8:41
if it's 1:00 in the morning in Miami,
bro, hold on. What day and time is it in
Miami? What the hell? What day and time
is it in Miami?
It is Friday
12:00 Okay, so it's 1:00 in the morning
in Miami.
Okay. So, that means that we are on our
final
London session. Wow, that
that actually changes everything.
Thank God. I was ready to take this
trade right now and I am not sure if I'm
ready to take this trade because it's
Friday. We have a perfect left head,
right shoulder right now cooking up. We
have a beautiful shift of structure.
EUR/USD could have the perfect like if
this does not have the move in the next
4 hours pretty much,
maybe even 8 hours max, we're pretty
much cooked, right? Because we'll be at
at market close.
Wow.
Wow, I really have to make a decision
here. I might just take this trade right
now. Uh dude, this whole time zone thing
is really messing me up. I'm I'm really
out of sync. This trade right here would
be a perfect trade if this were be
Tuesday, Wednesday, even Thursday. But
okay, because I'm seeing the morning and
I'm I don't even know what day it is,
but I'm seeing Friday 8:00 in the
morning and if it's Friday 8:00 in the
morning Miami time, that means that we
are basically headed towards the last 4
hours of New York session and the market
is about to close. But, if it's 1:00 in
the morning Miami time, we're about to
begin London session. So, we still have
all of London and whatever means
something of New York.
Yes, we might take this trade live right
now. I just don't know if it's worth it.
But, whatever. We have price basically
retesting
this area of interest. Daily time frame
broke the structure. It has been
accumulating for 1, 2, 3 days. Beautiful
bearish evening star pin bar rejection.
Beautiful, beautiful, beautiful,
beautiful, beautiful daily wick. I'm
anticipating for that wick to fill.
Beautiful 4-hour shift to structure left
head right shoulder retesting that
neckline.
Picasso.
Beautiful retracement and now we're
potentially going to be having that
bearish engulfing candle stick in the
next 60 minutes. I might say [__] it and
just enter this trade right now. I'm not
even going to lie. I I this trade is
just too nice.
Um GBP/CHF basically at the beginning of
the week we anticipated for this trade
from this area to have a push to the
upside and then it come back and have
the retest. That is exactly what we have
done.
And right now that we have done this
retest, we could uh
we can anticipate this trade to
have a reaction from the support.
Um yeah, this trade is cooking up so
fire for next week. Like I'm not even
Yeah, this is crazy. I'm going to be
here in Dubai probably for like the next
week or two and
this is cooking up the perfect trade for
that. Like this is a perfect trade for
next week. USD/CHF I was waiting for a
break and retest for next week and uh
looks like we are currently cooking that
up.
GBP/USD same exact thing. Looks like we
are cooking that up for this following
week. Right now we are at this We're
above this area of support and uh
obviously I cannot sell right into this
area. I have to wait for price to break
below that. So, it looks like we might
have this trade perfectly into next
week. Um GBP/AUD
nothing.
This is just uh I mean it had the move.
Basically the whole entire move happened
from this area. I think you guys already
know that. So, we missed out on this
trade. It is what it is.
But, we caught it perfectly.
NZD/CAD
We avoided this loss to perfection. So,
NZD/CAD I would have entered this trade
once again, probably probably a year
ago. This is a trade that I've been
avoiding pretty often lately. We had a
pullback into this area. I just wanted
to wait for a daily rejection. As I
would have waited for that daily
rejection, I would have realized that
price never stopped and you would have
continued going to the upside and I
would have avoided this loss. Even
though we had a perfect left head right
shoulder break at that neckline. But,
sometimes my experience requires me to
wait for extra confirmations and
sometimes it doesn't and sometimes it
works in my favor and sometimes it
doesn't. That is the nature of trading,
ladies and gentlemen. That is just that
that intuition and that decision making
at that point. USD/JPY So, exactly what
I said, if we pretty much come back
right below this area of interest, we're
just going to continue selling through
that zone. I've seen a lot of students
inside of my community that they
actually sold inside of this and they
were just they sold back to the bottom
of the zone. That was an uh that was a
possibility. I've been traveling the
majority of this week. Traveled for like
pretty much like 20 hours if you can
count
a flight like the whole logistics before
and after. So, I have I have just been
all over the place this week. I don't
So, I don't feel like I missed out on
much because market's really having
given me a big move aside from GBP/AUD.
AUD/USD had a break from this area. It's
now having the retest. I think this is
cooking up the perfect trade as well for
next week. Bro, next week is going to be
such a fire week. Here in Dubai is
crazy, too, right? Uh AUD/CHF
Yeah, nothing really on GBP on AUD/CHF
and your AUD I didn't even think I was
interested in this trade.
Yeah, I'm not going to lie. We we we
might take this EUR/USD trade, but now
factoring in that
factoring in that it's
the last London session of the week. I
don't like taking trades like this,
right? Let me just put my alarm below
here if it does
engulf for whatever reason, I'll make a
decision at that point, but
I don't know.
I'm just enjoying the view right now.
Honestly, bro, this is so like this is
pretty bad. This is pretty bad now that
I think about it because
I I think this I think this week is
setting up the perfect trade Like let's
say this does not happen this week,
right? Let's say this trade for whatever
reason does not happen. It just has to
consolidate. That sets up the perfect
trade for next week. And the reason why
that is bad
is because I am in Dubai right now. I am
I'm literally here. Like I am in Dubai
and if I actually enter this trade next
week, I will make
three, four, five hundred thousand
dollars. It's going to look so
>> [laughter]
>> fake.
Bro, it's going to look like I'm just
[__] doing some fugazi [__] but I'm
not. I This is just a perfect trade set
Bro, this is a perfect trade set up.
This is a perfect trade Like I am
literally going to make
probably half a million dollars next
week because of how fire these markets
are loading up. My timing to Dubai could
have not been better to be completely
honest.
Damn, I'm just going to look like
another one of these guys, bro.
I I I'm not going to get like a
Lamborghini or Ferrari. I'm not going to
rent one of those [__] cars out
here. I'm just going to
I'm going to get a BMW or whatever.
But, I'm just thinking.
Bro.
This is not good. I mean it's good, but
[__] I I almost want to like
I don't even know.
Cuz I want to make money. I I might just
do it and not post it cuz people I don't
want people to think I'm doing some [__]
just because I'm in Dubai. Like I'm
actually good, you know? Like I I really
trade like that.
I don't know.
Let's see what happens, boys, but this
is a perfect trade set up for next week.
I am not even going to lie. I'm very
excited for this, so I'll keep you guys
updated. Make sure to set them forget
and
I'll see you guys in the next next
couple of hours. And the rest of our
Friday pretty much consisted of we
worked out at the at the gym outside in
Dubai. Probably the most commonly known
gym. It was a mission to work out there
because of how hot it was. And then the
just a dinner with some of my team
members and kind of just getting used to
the time zone, getting ready for the
week ahead.
>> [music]
>> And on Saturday, the markets are pretty
much closed. So, what does a trader do
on the weekend?
Go to the world's deepest pool. That's
exactly what we did. I don't know if you
guys know, but I actually freedive all
the time and I broke my record for 27 m.
So, that's about 90 ft. I super crazy
fun fact, I can hold my breath for like
4 minutes. That's like actually one of
my superpowers.
>> [music]
[music]
>> And on Sunday we went to go meet up with
the Ono who brothers and we just chopped
it up, got to meet them in person. Like
we've been e-friends for a very long
time. Like you know, [music] text
messages, Instagram stuff.
This this gift This one's for you. Thank
you. Thank you. And then this one is for
you. Appreciate it, brother. And this
one's for like both of you guys
together, right? So, this is kind of
like a gift for you.
You guys can you guys Should I leave it
or open it? Or open it now? You guys can
open it now.
I think it kind of fits you guys
perfect. Bro, I was trying to get these
guys a gift. It took me I think we were
walking through the mall for like 3
hours, bro. I couldn't figure out what
to get you guys. It's difficult to
give give guys like us gifts. I I went
to Prada to get you guys a gift from
Prada, but This is sick. This is sick.
Is that Hermes ashtray? Sick ashtray,
man. This one's for good cigarette. It's
like exotic stuff, supposedly. I love
it, man.
Ah, this is my This is my color, man.
And I know you like blues, so cuz of
that the interior of the Rolls that's
for you, man.
Bro, we we went to Prada trying to get
you guys like a bag. And we talked to
like your Yeah, to you to Tracy? Yeah,
we talked to the Chinese guy. Yeah,
yeah, we talked to him.
And he comes in and he's like brother,
they bought everything.
>> [laughter]
>> And I'm like, all right, is is there
something they haven't gotten? And
they're like To be honest, we are top
spenders at Prada UAE.
I swear, that's why we got invited for
the I I I know you're a man who already
has it all, but this is one thing that
by far made me the most money in
business, so Yeah. You'll you'll you'll
you'll love this one. This is for you.
What does it say? I don't know. It's
just packaging, but you have [laughter]
to
look inside. Okay, let me see. So, this
is what has made you the most amount of
money? Yeah.
But, wow.
Who the formula to achieve bigger goals.
Who, not how. Yeah. So, the the concept
basically explains the fact that instead
of
every time you want to do or achieve
something or do something new for your
business, instead of how do I do this,
you change it to who can do this because
there are always people who already
walked the path and since I applied this
in business,
everything exploded and now we got
companies with
couple hundred employees. You know, you
saw
it.
>> We were even from prison, you know.
Exactly. we were zero involved with the
business till the business run. I was
killing [music] it.
That was a cool vibe and after we went
home, we did a Sunday Swings with the
students and I literally prepped with my
students and I told them, "Guys, this is
going to be a record-breaking week. We
will break the bank this week. The
banks, the markets will hear of us and
this move."
And little did we know
or little did I know that that was
actually going to come to fulfillment.
So, why you need to manifest everything
into [music] real life. And I posted it
on my Instagram. I literally said, "This
week I'm going to break my record. These
are the markets that I'm going to be
trading." On Instagram, I literally post
on Instagram, "This is what I'm going to
be doing for the week.
>> [music]
>> Feel free to take the trade at your own
risk, but this is exactly what I'm
doing." Does not get any more
transparent than that. Within I think an
hour, 300,000 people saw the video,
1,000 comments, and obviously some
people not believing in it. And those
people, guess what?
They still copied the trade. And I don't
think you guys understand how sharp and
how big this double-edged sword is. Like
I am literally publicly [music]
putting myself on the line saying,
"Everybody enter this trade. This is
what I'm going to be interested in
doing." Like this can go very good or
very bad. I could look like an absolute
fool if I were to lose this trade. And
if I were to win it exactly how I did, I
look great. And I literally explained to
the people this is going to move fast.
This is what I'm interested in. This is
why I posted it so soon. And that guess
what happened right on Monday morning. I
entered EUR/USD as soon as we break that
neckline of head and shoulders, and then
we entered EUR/GBP for the countertrend
trade. I explained all of this in the
video on Instagram. I shared it with it
my everything. And I explained to the
people exactly what we were looking
[music] to do into the trade. Within 2
hours, we had a massive candlestick that
actually took place right when I was
inside of the Forex Expo. So, at the
same time as I'm, you know, just meeting
random members from the community, as
I'm speaking to other business owners, I
am literally in the middle of a
record-breaking trade. My community is
going crazy. My DMs are going crazy. I'm
I'm getting all this type of of
abundance at the same time. I had to
lock myself in the bathroom for like 30
minutes just to like understand what was
going on because it was
9:00 in the morning, 10:00 in the
morning Dubai time zone as all of this
is happening. But then, this is like
3:00 in the morning EST. So, I just
completely did not have the connection
that we are inside of London session in
the prime time. And this whole time zone
thing happened at the same time, which
was fun because I I got to pretty much
go the rest about my day with the trade
moving massively, but also very
overwhelming because I didn't expect for
this trade to move that fast. Now, out
of all the markets that I had analyzed
on Sunday Swings with my students, my
number one pair was EUR/USD, number two
pair was AUD/USD, number three was
EUR/GBP, and four was AUD/USD. So, I
actually avoided GBP/CHF as the
countertrend high risk buy, and I
avoided the AUD/USD
buy as a loss. So, these were two losses
that I avoided and I actually entered
both of the winning trades. EUR/USD was
the best trade simply because it was the
least risk. It was the perfect protrend
trade. We're trading with the trend. We
are breaking the head the neckline of
head and shoulders. The trade is
absolutely perfect. And then EUR/GBP is
setting up the perfect countertrend
trade after the weekly high massive
weekly bearish engulfing candlestick.
We're basically entering at the lower
high to continue selling down. And my
decision-making on basically betting
that the euro was going to get weak for
that week was what made this the biggest
trade. So, this could have gone the
opposite way if the euro decided to get
strong, but I'm betting against the euro
with two currency pairs that for the
week I saw getting much stronger than
the euro, and that
affected my trade positively like you
can't even imagine. All I can say is
that I think this might be my biggest
trading week in a very long time. And
not because of monetary amount, because
I decided to do something that I've
never done in a very long time, and that
is literally share my exact signal on a
trade that I'm going to be interested in
taking. Like I'm going to go on social
media and I'm going to tell 200,000
people that watch my stories every
single day. Like this is not even cap
that you can literally look at this.
This is 200,000 people that see my
Instagram stories every single day. I'm
going to literally tell them, "Yo,
buy this, sell this." And I'm about to
break that down with you guys now. You
guys are going to get the full in-depth
explanation because on social media I'm
just going to say,
"Why did I decide to do this?
I don't know. I just wanted to challenge
myself. Honestly, I feel like
trading has become very easy for me
lately and I've been able to capitalize
off of it and do very well. And I just
want to help people all around the
world. I want people to be able to
capitalize off of it and use the money
that they make hopefully this week to
either, you know,
get a better trading account, uh get out
of some debts, get better education, or
just make some money. Hopefully, right?
There obviously is a risk associated
with this. If you want to copy my trade,
you need to understand there's a risk
associated with it. But I'm going to
make sure that I don't share my highest
risk trade setup. I'm going to make sure
that I do the best trade setup that it
doesn't have the highest probability of
losing, right? I'm not And I And it's
crazy, right? Because out of the trade
that I might share, I might share the
best prob like the best probability
trade setup and it still might be a
loser, and the higher risk trade might
have been the winner one. But you guys
are going to get the full breakdown on
every single trade, but I do see a very
very strong week coming. We're here in
Dubai right now. As you can tell, this
is the Burj Khalifa behind me, but it's
actually in front of me because it's the
reflection of the Burj Khalifa in the
building behind me or the glass behind
me, whatever.
So, another reason why I feel very
confident about this is because right
now it is currently
8:49 in the morning,
but it is technically 1:00 in the
morning Miami time. So, my day is about
to begin, and so is London session. So,
I am very confident not only about my
trades, but I'm literally going to be
fully awake when these markets give
these opportunities in London session in
pre-London session, during London
session, pre-New York session, during
New York session. I'm going to be fully
awake because the trading sessions
happen throughout the day. And I think
this is why there's so many traders here
in Dubai and why this type of the world
is very commonly traded on currency
markets because you're literally awake
as a regular person on the prime time
that the markets move. In Miami, it's
1:00 in the morning right now. I would
have to stay up all night for me to
catch a decent session in London. We're
here, it's the complete opposite. You
just wake up and have your normal day
and you're part of the market. So,
that's very cool. And that's another
reason why I feel very confident. And I
already tested this. I've been here for
a week already. I don't know how much
longer I'm going to be here. Maybe
another week, maybe 2 weeks. I already
tested it last week and it worked
perfectly. So, let's see how it works
this week, right? So, let's start
breaking it down. So, my first market
that I'm interested for the week was
EUR/USD.
EUR/USD last week I've been very
interested since trading it. But right
now we are at an all-time high, and this
all-time high had a massive liquidity
grab with this very strong weekly
bearish pin bar breaking through all
these highs. We are very much bullish.
This market has had a very strong clean
push to the upside, but we're
approaching this strong resistance level
that we haven't broken above since 2021,
right? And right now we are simply just
below this level, and that is a fact.
The daily time frame has currently
shifted bearish. This was the higher
low. This is the higher high. Now we are
bearish retesting this area of interest
once again, and we've had a very clean
daily shooting star evening star
engulfing candlestick. Now, what I see
here on the 4-hour is a beautiful 4-hour
accumulating at this area of interest.
This is creating a beautiful left head
right shoulder multiple right shoulders.
But what I see here at the most
important is a neckline. This neckline
of this head and shoulders. Now,
I want price to break this neckline of
the head and shoulders so that I can
enter the trade to the downside. This is
not quite there just yet. I believe that
this market from this point right here
could potentially
have a clean rejection from here. Like
maybe this is the exact area where it
actually has the push, but I need that
push and that retest for me to enter the
trade to the upside. I want to enter the
trade at the bottom of this area. I
don't want to enter the trade at the top
of this area because price could
basically come, use this as support as
it's done in the past, and then have a
push to the upside. I want to wait till
price gets below it because clearly
whenever we are below this area, price
clearly continues going to the downside.
Do I get a little bit worse of an entry?
Sure, but I get a much better
confirmation on my trade as a whole.
That's what I personally want if I'm
going to be sharing with 200,000 people
the trade that I'm going to be
interested in taking. So, I'm have my
alarm set up right here so if price
notifies me once and if we ever decide
to do that.
Next is going to be NZD/USD.
Very similar to EUR/USD, but this one
looks much much cleaner.
Hopefully this week
this gentleman right here or this
gentleman right here
won't be out for a while, but yeah,
hopefully doesn't do us dirty in the
markets this week because
yeah, that would not be fun. Right now,
NZD/USD we have a massive bearish
engulfing candlestick now retesting this
structure. Daily time frame we are now
currently retesting this area of
interest. And now that we're retesting
this area of interest, I then go down to
the 4-hour and I see that the 4-hour is
currently potentially creating a head
and shoulders. Same exact thing as
EUR/USD. I need a break and retest of
this neckline for me to enter this trade
to the downside. Very simple. It's
basically the exact same trade. This is
just a lot further from this neckline.
EUR/USD is a lot closer to this
neckline.
Next we have EUR/GBP. This is the one
trade where it is a degenerate trade.
This is a very high risk trade, but I
think it might be ready to take
like right now as we speak. Maybe in the
next 8 minutes. I'd wait probably for
this candlestick to close, but
left head right shoulder,
[clears throat]
break this neckline, retesting it. It's
like the perfect counter trend trade
setup.
>> [sighs and gasps]
>> But that's the problem. It's a counter
trend trade setup. It is a perfect trade
setup for this to literally
Cuz like we're expecting for price to
have a retracement to this area, right?
So right now we've had a Technically
this market is bullish. We've had a push
up, but I believe this needs a better
retest of this area before continuing
heading to the upside. And last week we
had a massive weekly bearish engulfing
pin bar candlestick. I expect this week
to be the fill of that.
Um we are technically retesting below
this minor daily area of interest right
here. So this is our resistance,
resistance, support. We're retesting it.
The 4-hour time frame probably has the
cleanest head and shoulders I've seen
this week. This is the cleanest head and
shoulders that you can possibly ask for
right here. Like everything that I would
have wanted to take a counter trend
trade is right here, but I don't know if
I want to share a counter trend trade in
front of 200,000 people. Like this is a
not the brightest idea in my opinion,
but the trade might be there.
Oh man, it's like a love-hate thing cuz
you ask for all of these extra
confirmations and then the market does
it.
And then
you ask yourself, does it make sense to
take the trade or not?
It's a great question.
>> [snorts]
>> It's a great question.
I'll wait. I'm going to wait these 6
minutes and I'll we'll come back to it.
We'll get through this quick. GBPCHF, we
are basically at the all-time low,
literally the lowest point we have ever
take lowest point we've ever been in
this market. This is an extremely
high-risk degenerate trade. I do not
suggest this trade to anybody, but if
you were to take it, this is like this
is the trade that I would probably take
and not share, but this is like the
perfect degenerate trade where at the
lowest point we've ever been. The 4-hour
time frame right now I'm going to be
waiting for price to have a break and
retest above this area here. So I have
this like big bullish candle in case we
actually end up doing that.
Let me actually delete this alarm. I
don't know why there's two alarms here,
but I I need this alarm to get hit right
around here for this market to let me
know once we're shifting, rejecting this
left head right shoulder, this inverted
neckline of the head and shoulders for
me to take this trade to the upside.
GBPAUD, I broke this down last night
with my students. If it closes with a
strong engulfing, I'd be interested in
selling the trade. The trade had a
stronger engulfing than I anticipated.
Trade had a pretty aggressive move. Not
really in the business to chase this
trade. I literally broke this down last
night on Sunday swings with my students.
By the way, if you guys have not
subscribed to this channel, literally
subscribe to this channel. I break down
every single one of the pairs that I do
with my students as detailedly as I
possibly can. It's kind of give you guys
the overview, but with my students every
single Sunday, I literally give them
these exact trades, a much deeper call
on why I'm interested in these markets
and why I'm not interested in these
other 25 other markets. So I give them
the breakdown of the ones that make the
most sense and the ones that don't. So I
find these markets every single week
with my students and I actually explain
to them in a much deeper way that I am
doing right now why I'm interested in
entering some trades and why I'm not
interested in others. But yeah, if you
guys want to know more about that, check
the link in the description below and
hit the subscribe button because I want
this channel to be
my new way of
educating people in trading with
real-life raw markets. If you guys
aren't subscribed, you're not going to
get this reminder.
AUDUSD, we have a perfect weekly bullish
engulfing candlestick last week.
Beautiful pro trend trade, retesting
this area here. Like this trade is
perfect. Daily time frame, we have a
daily retest of this area, break above
this area, retest of this area right
here. 4-hour time frame, it currently
seems to be creating a perfect
shift of structure.
This one just looks good as well. Oh
man.
I'm going to be waiting for a little bit
of a retest and on this retest if I get
an engulfing, I'm going to enter this
trade to the upside. I love how the
daily looks.
I love how the 4-hour looks.
I love how
I love how this market is just moving as
a whole on this area right here. So
we're going to wait for this one as
well. I just moved it up cuz I actually
like this market a lot.
AUDJPY we broke down. EURAUD,
this one I just believe it's just going
to continue going to the downside. If
the daily could close like this, that
would be massive cuz then I would enter
off of the next day. I don't want to
enter off of today's move. I feel like
it would be an impulse move. I want this
market to have the continuation push to
the downside and then I'll wait for the
retest for us to enter this trade to the
downside. So it'll be a quick break,
retest, and then I'd be interested in
selling. Basically what we did here,
break, retest, sell. Right now we're
just having that break. I'll wait for
the retest.
GBPCHF GBPUSD, we're going to be waiting
for this to have a proper break and
retest, so we are yet to do that. And
USDCHF a proper break and retest.
Basically once this price breaks and
retests this neckline of the head and
shoulders, retests this EMA, I'm going
to be interested in taking this trade to
the downside. I'd say right now my
priority is indeed AUDUSD.
EURGBP
and EURUSD for a sell. So let me just
bring Let me organize all these markets
right here. Yeah, so these are my top
three markets right now. EURUSD for a
sell,
AUDUSD for a sell, and this is where
some people get confused. They're like,
"Wait, but here you're going to be
selling the dollar or yeah, basically
selling the buy buying the dollar. Here
you're going to be selling the dollar.
How do you do that?" Well, I just pick
whichever one makes the most sense and
then I take it. And you guys also have
to remember there's two other currency
pairs on this market right here that
influence greatly this market. So we
can't just take a trade based off of the
USD. Obviously the USD is the stronger
currency and it's going to primarily
move this market, but these other
currency pairs will have a great effect
on it.
And then we also have the counter trend
trade, so
let me think about it. I'll cook it up
right now. I want to focus and see
exactly what I'm going to do and what
the decision
I'm going to take. I'll update you guys
now.
So after this first initial push of the
trade moving massively in my direction,
the trade pretty much stalled throughout
the rest of the day.
And showed a couple of the students that
were there at the expo that wanted to
see the trade live. I showed it to them
live. I showed them my account history,
showed them that it was a real account,
showed them everything, right? Cuz you
know some students are like, "Bro, I
want to see it." It's motivation to see
that in person. And after doing that,
basically went out to dinner once again
with the team and the market slows down.
Can you like can you show me a live
trade? Is that possible? A live trade?
Yeah, people are going to think this is
fake, bro. People are going to think
this is fake. Is it a live one? What?
All right, it's it's the Wi-Fi. Let it
You got to give it a second.
Can you go on the Can you go on the
broker?
>> Looking 400.
It's great. Can you show any other other
trades you took like past P&L or broker
statement or something like
Cuz many people say you're a scammer, so
I don't But I don't believe it. Okay,
okay. I hear the hater from the
comments.
Let's
>> [laughter]
>> Let's see the real money. Okay, so this
like the trade is live, right? Like I'm
literally I'm in this trade. So I'm
You're selling euros. Yeah, like I'm I'm
literally posting it right now on my
Instagram and people are watching it.
I'm literally posting it right now. What
did you take short on euros? Yeah, so
look, this student right here Look, this
Look, look, this student in my community
just posted 1 hour ago
and he also caught the trade and he made
$22,000.
Huh? He closed already. Yeah, yeah,
look, it's it's a it's a closed position
right here. Look, 22. I'm literally as
you speak you walked up to me as I was
taking a screenshot of this trade right
here.
I must have a hell of screenshots,
right?
That's what I was doing right now, yeah.
Trade out there real quick.
Um
That's what I get for flexing on
Instagram.
314,000.
Let's go home.
>> [music]
[music]
>> The next day, it's the exact same thing.
We go back to the Forex Expo. So where
this is Tuesday now, and the market is
starting to have a retracement. So
EURUSD has pulled back into retest the
neckline of the head and shoulders. So
the trade being from $200,000 in profit
just one single trade is now negative
$10,000 or $15,000. The trade came back
to break even and I explained to
everybody. I even posted it on Twitter.
People were asking me on Twitter cuz I
shared this trade on Twitter. I said,
"Yo, I'm interested in taking these
three trades. Please trade at your own
risk." My comment section, my DMs were
blowing up. Alex, the trade is back.
What should I do? And I literally said,
set and [__] forget. That is exactly
what we do at this point. We commit to
the trade. We either let the trade get
taken out of stop loss or let the trade
take out at break even.
And guess what happened on Tuesday.
The trade flew the [__] take profit
because we set and [__] forget. So
all the students came up to me at the
expo,
uh people that literally met me at the
expo that I explained to them what was
going on with the trade, entered the
trade, and the trade played out
massively. It was just a trend
continuation trade. It could have not
gotten any easier than that. All right,
ladies and gentlemen, update. There's
just so much that has gone down since
the last time I recorded this.
Let's just start breaking some things
down, I guess. Just so much has
happened. So EURUSD obviously had a very
strong sell-off. We basically sold off
of the sell-off, came back, retested it,
massive daily bearish engulfing
candlestick with a bearish pin bar.
Today we have filled that and we have 5
hours left in this candlestick to close.
Right now it's currently 11:46 in the
morning
EST. So we're waiting for this to
continue having a push to the downside.
It's moving very clean. 4-hour closes
structure below. We've obviously been in
both of these positions, well, this one
and then the other one.
So we got a an upgraded account on the
broker that we're using, so we're able
to finally do more than 90 lots. That 90
lot [__] was extremely annoying, but
right now we're up probably $843,000
on this trade. So, we're up actually
half a mil on this trade and I called it
to perfection on EUR/USD. AUD/USD, we
dodged this bullet and EUR/GBP, we
caught this sell to perfection.
Beautiful entry right after this
rejection. Beautiful push to the
downside. Hit we held through like
[__] menace to society
and we are now having this
>> [laughter]
>> It's just so crazy that I actually held
all the way down. It's just insane. And
I'm going to continue to hold this
position down, but basically this
countertrend trade has happened. NZD/USD
is currently cooking up another trade
right now and I think it's going to
basically cook this up for tomorrow,
right? I would not enter a trade right
now after this daily bearish engulfing
candlestick. I'm going to wait for a
wick pullback into this area and after
this wick pullback is then when I'm
going to be interested in the sells, but
this so far has been playing out to
perfection as well. So, I have that
noted. GBP/CHF,
if we would have entered this trade,
we'd be in a little bit of a
consolidation. Daily looks like it's
creating another daily doji as well, so
I'd be very interested in entering this
trade as well later into this week after
retesting of this engulfing
and GBP/AUD
had the move to the downside, bounce off
of here and now having the move back to
the upside. Not that interested into
this trade anymore. Basically this trade
has already pretty much just happened.
The trade is gone. Not that interested.
EUR/AUD had a little bit of move,
nothing.
GBP/USD, nothing and USD/CHF, nothing.
Our main focus is to continue to hold
EUR/USD. AUD/USD maybe for some
potential buys, not really. Going to
continue holding these sells on EUR/GBP
for the next couple of hours to see how
the daily time frame closes. NZD/USD is
my next trade that I'm going to be
interested in taking in 100%. We're
going to put it as our number one pair
and GBP/CHF is going to be another trade
that I'm going to be very interested in
executing as well. Have to wait for this
daily time frame to close in the next
couple of hours. So,
yeah, it's pretty much everything for
now. Not the
most active week. I've just been in
Dubai. We went to the Forex Expo.
I did a you know, met a couple of cool
guys out here and I think for the first
time in
years
I'm actually enjoying
not recording stuff and I'm just like
actually living life and it's pretty
cool.
So, I I I'm kind of just enjoying it,
right? And
I think tomorrow we're going to go to
the lions. So, one of my rich friends
here, part of the royal family, has like
a lion tiger. So, we're going to go to
that tomorrow
and
I probably will not do an update. Sorry,
but I explained it here and maybe we
come back the day after and then I show
you guys. I think this is the first time
I'm actually like not prioritizing
the work. I'm prioritizing like just
living in the moment and I'm
I'm loving it. I'm having a great time.
And I think that these trades are just
so simple. I say them every single week
inside this channel. If you guys follow
along, you guys know. You guys know I'm
literally just like repeating myself
with new examples every single week and
you guys are capitalizing off of it. I
literally posted on my Twitter.
Literally posted on my Twitter
this trade
to perfection. I literally posted me
explaining this trade. I mean, you guys
can editor, please please pop it up.
Screenshots of my Twitter here of me
literally just sending these trades out
here publicly telling people to continue
to hold. These are the last three trade
ideas. This is all like live, right?
Like, you know, what do you have about
how many was that? 66,000 people saw
this. Like I literally said EUR/USD
sell, AUD buy and then yeah.
I think you guys get the point. Set and
[__] forget. And honestly, this
trade was supposed to stop at half a
million. Like that was where I was going
to cap the trade out. That was where it
peaked at half a mil
and it got to the point where I got a
little bit greedy and I said, you know
what? We're going to continue to set and
[__] forget. And little that I
realized I was setting and forgetting
the wrong trade, which is EUR/GBP.
EUR/GBP is a countertrend trade. I
should cut my profits fast, right?
Because I'm taking a trade against the
trend. But I decided to commit and
EUR/GBP decided to have a retracement
off there. It actually already made it
to my take profit, which is at a strong
support level. After that retracement,
EUR/GBP then continued to push down
creating a new lower low making the euro
weaker and that is exactly what made
EUR/USD continue to break low and
continue to head to the downside and
that's where everything changed. That's
where this went from a half a million
dollar trade to a $700,000
trade. All of this by Tuesday,
Wednesday. [music] And I expected for
this to be a million dollar week because
of all of the trades that I was going to
execute. I was probably going to execute
a total of three trades, max four. I've
actually never taken more than that
amount of trades in a single week, but
there were so many perfect opportunities
that I said, you know what? This might
be the week. But my decision-making
changed in the middle of the week
because I had such great entries on
these trade that I was going I was
continuously fishing for that million
dollar week, but just with the same
exact trades. People always want to make
more money from the markets by taking
more trades and you don't make more
money from the markets by making more
trades. You make more money from the
markets by letting the right trade
continue to make you more money. If
you're trading with the trend, you're on
the right side of the market and you
have a solid risk to reward you let that
trade ride. That's how you're going to
maximize your profits, not by entering
another trade. You just simply let a
winning trade continue be a winning
trade. That is the whole philosophy
behind set and forget. That is how you
continuously It's like making passive
income. If you entered the right trade
setup and the trade is hot, you let it
do its thing. The last thing you want to
do is cut your profits short. You always
want to cut your losses short because
you don't ever want to lose more money,
but you always want to make more money
and if it doesn't cost you more money to
make more money
why would you close out that trade
setup? You're making more money off of
the same trade you already took without
having any additional risk. That is the
beauty of set and forget and entering
the right trade setup. That's exactly
what I did. The trades were having very
strong momentum. They were heading in my
direction. Why would I cut a trade short
that has strong momentum in my
direction?
I won't and that's why it made me the
profits that it did. Boy, so we're back
for day two.
I wasn't going to come today for day
two, but I said, you know what? All of
my Indian people out here, we had such a
[__] good time yesterday that I need
to come again today. I need to meet the
people.
I I didn't say that I was coming
yesterday. I just pulled up and I just
posted like when I was leaving. Bro, I
think I got
3,000 DMs that people were going to pull
up today if I were to just pull up and
like if I'm on this side of the world, I
want to meet you guys. So, I said, [__]
I'm just pulling up. Not letting them
know I'm here but
trade update.
Trade is looking pretty decent. So,
yesterday we had a retracement back into
the retesting of this neckline.
EUR/GBP
still in profit
as we speak.
Trade right now is uh
300k.
No, it's bad.
Good to see you here. Bro, I'm excited,
bro. I'm excited.
I I didn't even know you were like a
main sponsor for this either.
Forex.
>> [laughter]
>> Look, right now right now I'm up Oh my
god. Wait, it's it's going to lower.
You're up 300 or 100? 356.
Like I was up half a mil yesterday, but
I'm up He's up he's up $350,000.
>> I lost 150 grand. I'm like making it
back now. I'm trying.
Yeah, like if this trade closes in
profit, I'll be like 800. By the way,
you got the watch. Oh yeah, black or
red? Black or red?
I'm going to play for money. I'm going
to play for money. No chance.
Okay, red red red. Yeah. All right.
Guys.
We're here doing Forex stuff.
Red. Wow. 50 million dollars, guys. I
think
Oh [__] That's crazy.
Brilliant. Good to see you here.
That's the man right there, man. So,
this is one of my most profitable
students. We did podcast one. We did
podcast two. Oh my god, bro. I didn't
even realize.
Oh, check it. All right, look. Now, wait
wait wait for it. Perfect days. All
right.
You can't fake this [__] Can't fake
that [__]
So, after we left the Forex Expo, which
is the second and final day, I said, you
know what? This is going to be a winning
trade.
>> [music]
>> Let's go celebrate. And what a better
way of celebrating by buying another
watch. And not a new watch.
The same watch I already have. Why?
Cuz why the [__] not?
>> [snorts]
>> I have a Jacob and Co. Black and red,
right? So, the the whole roulette is
black or red and sometimes I can't make
a decision whether to pick black or red.
And my Jacob and Co. has red straps, so
I said, okay, you know what? Let me get
another one with a black strap. So, if I
don't know which one to pick, I just
wear them both.
That's what I did.
Bro, the box is crazy. I've not seen a
box like that. Fair enough. This is
definitely like the hottest box, bro. I
have a doubt.
Bro, having two of these is going to be
crazy.
Yeah, no. As in your is hard. Definitely
for sure. All right, so basically we're
going to Bro, we should do like at the
same time.
So, we're going to flip or spin for a
thousand difference or two thousand
difference? What was the difference? A
thousand, right? A thousand difference?
Okay, so we're spinning for a thousand
right now. Let's see who wins. What
color do you want to pick?
I'll leave it to you. I'll go black for
black. So, that's how
>> [laughter]
>> All right, let's spin it on the black.
On the black. All right, you want to do
it on the black watch or the red on the
black watch? Go for black. I'll let you
spin it. This is too many odds against
us here. I'm not going to like
All right, spinning it.
God, this thing spins way more than
mine. I'm not going to lie.
Red than black, bro. Smaller balls over
there.
Red than green.
And
red.
For the thing you better appreciate you.
This is sick. All right. Well, now
>> Jeez. I just left that here with another
free one on the other wrist, you know?
No, I thought it was black and red
slaps, right?
I think you should keep the black, bro.
>> It's It's just cuz you're black, but
that's why you want to keep the dollar.
Guys, that's where the color came.
I mean, guys Thank you, boss. Pleasure
for coming down, bro. No, it was a
pleasure. Beautiful. Appreciate you, my
brother. Yeah, thank you really much,
Jared. All right. So, trade up there
right now. EUR/USD is having a
continuation push to the downside,
looking very very solid. AUD/USD, we
avoided this last to perfection. So,
this trade was avoided. And EUR/GBP is
having a major retracement. So, not
going to lie, pretty big L on my end
right here for not closing this trade
down over here. So, we would be up so
much more right now. We would be up 275
here plus the 250 that I was up on this
one. We'd be up like 600 grand right
now, but I decided to get greedy and
continue to hold this one. This is a
counter trend trade. So, this trade we
did not anticipate for it to make it all
the way back,
you know, like this is like we're
supposed to be buying here, basically.
And we still decided to continue to hold
this trade. It has so much more downside
potential. We will continue to hold this
position.
And that right there shows you boys get
out [__] balls. Balls of [__]
steel.
Two big [__] balls for holding
the [__] trade through some drawdown,
a little bit of a retracement. Now, fast
forward to Wednesday morning after
having a probably the best night sleep
I've ever had because
now when I sleep in this time zone, I'm
actually sleeping [music] in the trading
sessions that have no volume. So, my
trade is going to be good. It's not like
Miami time zone where I fall asleep and
I wake up to a surprise. Either the
trade is going to be at my stop loss or
be at my take profit. So, stressing is
always
Sleeping is actually very stressful in
the EST time zone. So, I fall asleep,
normal. I wake up 8:00 in the morning,
which is pre-London session. And I
decided, you know what? Let's give it
another hour cuz I want to see what
happens right at the crack of London
session. Maybe there's an additional
volume that can actually push my trade a
little bit further into profit. And
that's where I started seeing the trade
just jitter too fast into one direction
and then the other one. And I said, you
know what? I'm going to make the
executive decision at this point and
close out this trade. I'm about to close
out my biggest profits in a single day
for $738,000.
Now, before I close this trade out live
right now, I think it's so much cooler
than me making money that I just shared
this on social media 2 days ago and tens
of thousands, if not hundreds of
thousands of people were able to
capitalize off of this just off of a
[__] Instagram video. Yo, genuinely
speaking, if you guys made money off of
this trade, comment it down below.
Anything. If you guys were to actually
If you guys even saw this happen in real
time and you guys followed it and you
guys did it, just just comment it. You
guys have no idea how much that
motivates me and it keeps me going to
just continue to do this for you guys.
So, let's close out my biggest profits
in a single day here together. So, we're
going to go to bulk operations.
And we're going to close our positions.
Bang.
>> [laughter]
>> This trade is already past my take
profit. So, my take profits were set for
a 1:2 risk to reward. We're at a 1:2.3,
1:2.5 on the other trade setup. And I
personally set and forget until the
trade gets to my take profit. Once the
trade gets to my take profit, then there
I analyze the market structure and
decide if it makes sense to continue to
set and forget. And it did continue It
did make sense to continue to set and
forget. But honestly, I was looking at
the money. I was saying, you know what?
This is my biggest trading profits I've
ever made in a single week. It might not
be the full million dollars that I want,
but I'm not going to be greedy. I'm just
coming off of a 2-week losing streak and
then a whole entire week where I did not
execute a trade.
I kind of need this money right now. So,
let me actually close out my profits for
the week and lock in something. And
that's exactly what I did. Now, I looked
at the markets 6 hours later and yes, I
missed out on probably the other
$250,000
that I needed to make my million
dollars. But you know what? I did not
feel any type of way simply because I
locked in the profits that I risked for
and that I aimed to get. Anything after
my take profit, whatever happens after
that, I don't get emotional and I don't
care about it because at the moment of
me closing the trade, I made a decision
based off of a cool and calm mindset.
And at that time, it made sense to do
that. So, I am not going to regret my
decision or think back on it and say,
"Damn, I would have could have, should
have made so much more." No. You made
money, you move on. There's going to be
another opportunity. That's the problem
with a lot of traders out there is that
they don't have that type of mindset.
Whether they win a trade and they could
have made more money, they start
thinking of the what ifs. And if they
miss out on the trade, they think of,
"Well, what if I would have risked
more?" And if they lose a trade, they're
like, "Well, what if I never took it?"
No. I don't I don't think of the what
ifs. I don't think of the hypotheticals.
I made a decision. It made sense. I made
money. I move on. Simple.
>> [laughter]
>> I'm not even supposed to like be Oh,
man.
We're up $716,000.
This is [__] insane. The fact that
I'm up nearly a million dollars in just
3 days is absolutely insane. Coming from
somebody that like I'm I I I've made a
[__] ton of money. But this is like an
unfathomable amount of money for such a
little amount of time and such a little
amount of effort. Like I haven't done
[__] anything. All I've just done is
execute a trade and just wait. Yes, this
trade came back, could have taken me out
at break even. I could have even lost
some money, but that's just the risk
that I took behind the trade, but
the fact that I'm up $720,000
on a [__] Wednesday, it is it is just
mind-blowing to me right now.
And
I feel it's like I I came here to Dubai.
I was here for a week. I understood
how the trading time zones worked. I saw
the markets cooking up for next week and
I capitalized off of that. I set a goal
for myself. I manifested it. I put it
out into there. I'm like, "Yo, this week
I want to make a [__] million
dollars."
So, some people might look at me like
I'm crazy. Some people might look at me
like this is a unrealistic goal. Some
people might look at me and and think
it's fake.
But I'll tell you this,
I'm the [__] that's up right now
$718,000.
I'm the [__] that called it. I'm
the [__] that that that put it
out there.
And now it's here.
It's kind of crazy. I I I don't know.
It's just uh
uh
I mean, you guys are going to be
watching this, who knows from where in
the world. And I I'm just experiencing
it here now and it's it's very real.
And
you know, I'm not here to just like
flex. I'm not here to
[__] on you or I'm just here to show you
what's possible. I'm here to show you
the transparency behind it. And
if I can do it, so can you. All right.
So,
you guys can see right here yesterday, I
was literally explaining the only trade
I was interested in entering was
NZD/USD. I needed that break. I needed
that retest to sell.
And yeah, we never got that [__]
retest and we never sold. But you know
what? It's okay. So, we predicted
another market. This is another
beautiful execution of another trade
following the strategy. Like, bro,
there's so much free money this week. I
told bro, this is so crazy.
Oh, man. This is so crazy. I literally
told you guys yesterday the daily time
frame closes bearish engulfing like
this, we're going to wait for a little
pullback to then sell. 4-hour time frame
has had no pullback. So, since it had no
pullback, we simply did not get to enter
the sell. But the move was right there.
The head and shoulders was right there.
The break. Even the retest, but the
retest happened too late into the day.
EUR/USD,
my boys, we are up the 1:2 risk to
reward. We have officially hit our take
profit. And we are now approaching this
level of support. I very strongly
believe that we are going to have a
reaction from this support level right
here. I do believe that this can
potentially have, you know, have this
create a push to the upside. If not, I
believe this will close very strong
engulfing and just keep going down. I'm
probably not going to be in that trade
for that long. I like this to me is
already good. I caught the right
shoulder or the retest of the neckline
to the support level. I'm pretty much
done right at this level here.
Um GBP/CHF
has had a very strong reaction from this
level of support. I was looking at it
earlier. So, right now it's 8:30 in the
morning here and it's 12:30 in Miami.
So, we're about to enter London session.
Like it's it's only the middle of the
week. We are still only getting started.
Like this or this looks like it's about
to fly.
This to me looks like it's about to take
off.
Uh
this this is just creating a perfect
base at this level.
I might just enter this other I I
literally just might enter this trade
cuz [__] it.
I might I'm going to enter on on one of
my other accounts. Yeah, I'm going to
enter on another account. Let me give
you a second.
Uh what phone is [__] it. It's on the
other phone. But I'm I'm going to I'm
going to enter
this buy right here. We'll just put this
along. I'm going to wait for
Uh yeah, I'll wait for this candlestick
to close in the next 28 minutes. This
AUD GBP/AUD, we're going to continue to
go.
EUR/GBP has had a very strong push to
the downside and we've capitalized off
of this whole entire move. Even with
this retracement right here, we've
continued to set and forget. Let the
trade come back into this area. We're
going to potentially be interested in
closing very soon here simply because I
don't believe that
this has more downside potential. I
believe this is a pro trend trade and
this is the area where it can
potentially have a reaction from and
then it can obviously have a push up or
it could take it and it can literally do
this, have a massive weekly bearish
engulfing and then continue having a
push down, but I've already capitalized
off of this more than I should have. I
don't need any more. It would obviously
it would be cool, but I I I'm very
content. So, I know I I wanted to make a
million dollars this week, but
I think I'm just good with the 700
grand. I'm not going to lie.
Yeah, I think I'm just going to take
this 710 and run with it because
I don't even want to risk
Like this is good. This is good. Ah,
I'll keep my eye on it. Basically,
NZD/USD we missed it. GBP/CHF we
continue to have the move.
>> [clears throat]
>> And you know, you guys have I feel you
guys have seen like a different side of
me this week because I'm out of my
regular routine in my home. I'm out of
my
time zone. I'm out of just like
what built me as a person. I'm just out
of my my system, my routine. I love my
routine.
I love what I built and and I don't give
that up for anybody. I don't give that
up for anything and I that's what got me
to the point where I am now. And being
able to still thrive and succeed out of
my routine, out of my environment just
shows what you have a proven concept,
what the [__] you can do, you know? I
don't know. It's pretty exciting, pretty
cool. I I'm actually having a great
time.
So, I haven't had a great time in a
while. So,
we're going to close out this trade
probably in in the next 30 minutes to an
hour cuz I want to see what London
session could do. Maybe it could give me
some more profit.
And we're going to go chill with some
lions and tigers.
Hopefully not get eaten on I doubt it,
but
I don't know. It's pretty crazy. That's
all That's all I can say. I just keep
saying that. It's pretty crazy. I feel
like I'm young again in a way.
>> [laughter]
>> I feel like I'm young again because like
once you like when you get so successful
and and you make so much money so fast,
I like you kind of like lose touch with
a lot of things. Like there's no
supercar, there's no hypercar, there's
no car that's going to like wow me
anymore, right? But doing something like
this that I'm doing right now is just
wowing me.
Making a [__] ton of money out of my
home while I'm traveling and having fun
is just like this new feeling. It's like
this new high that I've just gotten
right now. I I'm just enjoying this cuz
right now in like I could be up this
money in Miami and all right, now I'm
just you know, I'd go to my my gym. I'd
I'd just be in my routine and that's all
what I built and what I created and I
loved, but it's not it's not new, it's
not exciting. And I feel like this right
now is just new and exciting and and I
and I'm loving it. That's all I can say.
So, last update we are up 710,000.
We'll update you guys later. See you
boys. So, after closing my trade, I was
very happy and it was a great day to go
with one of my friends Mo Vlogs to to
the zoo. So, you got a couple rich
friends out there that have zoos. I
don't know, you know, like that's
different type of money. If you have
your own private zoo, you're rich rich.
And uh I almost got raped by an
orangutan.
Yeah, that was weird.
Abu Abu
Hey. Oh, that's
juicy about that knee. Oh my god, what
is it doing?
It was like sucking. No, it's like
screwing. Bro, maybe he has a kink for
knees.
>> Bro, that's some weird [__] going on.
Come on.
Come on. Come on.
Bro, this looks so crazy.
So, after nearly getting my kneecap
bitten off by a chimp or an orangutan,
I felt rich. I felt very rich after
leaving the royal palace after being
with cool animals and making nearly a
million dollars in a day, I told Mo, Mo,
I need a kandura.
Cuz I'm that guy now. I am a habibi now
officially. Please give me the the honor
to take me to my first kandura.
That's exactly what I did. And
supposedly I look like
some famous guy from there. I don't
know, but let's say I I bought more than
one. Shout out to Mo for actually
gifting me my first kandura.
Habibi.
>> [laughter]
>> Okay, so so this is supposed to stay
like this, okay?
>> Now you look like a Bugatti owner.
>> 100%.
>> Now this is the guy who owns a Bugatti.
>> [laughter]
>> Shoes? Shoes or no shoes? No, no, no no
shoes. You need slippers. You need
slippers. Slippers, yeah.
Yeah, we take slippers. Thank you very
much.
Yeah, Mo Mo just got me my first
kandura. Thank Thank you. You're now
you're now official. Thank you very
much.
>> Welcome to Dubai. Yo, we're rocking
around like this.
>> [laughter]
>> So, at this point after I have my
kandura and I have just nearly made a
million dollars in one single week and
I've pretty much just stunted on other
people that don't believe in me or think
that I'm a demo trader or a fake trader,
I decided to let it out in the Twitter
community and the X community, the
people that are the the friendliest or
are very uh
aggressively friendly. And I I don't
mean to come off as an arrogant person.
I'm not an arrogant person. I'm really
not. I may say some things which
probably don't have the best grammar
come off a bit aggressive, but I I mean
it in the best way. It's like tough
love. And then I did this other tweet
and it's kind of funny cuz some people
when they come up to me in person,
they're like, "Yo, Alex, you're actually
a really nice guy. Like I don't know why
I thought I thought you'd be a
dickhead." Like why would you think I'm
a [__] I mean I I I read this tweet
that I posted. I'm like, "Well, I can
see how I can come off a little arrogant
sometimes." But I do it because I just
don't I hate arguing with small-minded
people in the industry, honestly. It to
me is a [__] waste of time. So, I
said here, "Haters love me. I called the
moves. Simple. Call it demo money if you
want. I'll be withdrawing my demo funds
and eating wagyu."
Set and forget.
Okay, fine. It's a little arrogant, but
it always be it always be the the the
the the non-believers, the haters that
are the ones saying, "It's demo, it's
real, it's not fake." Okay, let's let's
say the trade let's say I'm trading
demo. [__] it. All right, I'm trading
demo. You caught me. Cool.
Can you at least give me credit that I'm
predicting the trades? Am I not
literally saying that the trade is going
to go from this point to this point and
then to continue to hold? Do you just
think I'm going to predict this and not
actually risk money behind it?
In what [__] right mind does that
make sense?
That's why I don't argue with
small-minded people and uh
we set and forget them. And uh I
realized that this got me a little bit
emotional in a greedy way where I
started feeling like the man and I
started thinking that I I almost felt
like
I could predict every single move in the
market and [music] that's when I went
back to the market to go trade again.
Now, thankfully, I've been doing this
for a long time for 7 years and I made a
great analysis in the market and it was
literally another perfect trade setup
where I would take this trade setup 10
out of 10 times. But you know what? I
made a rule where I don't take more than
two trades in a single week. If I take
more than two trades in a single week, I
have to do something to hold myself
accountable. For example, taking cold
showers, right? If I if I break my rule,
I have to go ahead and take a cold
shower. And I'm going to be honest,
>> [music]
>> I did not want to take a cold shower, so
I decided to, "You know what? I already
made a lot of money this week. I'm not
going to take a trade. We're going to
leave it like that." And I was really
wanting to make a million dollars for
the week just so I can complete my goal
for the week. And me following my
trading plan, I decided to not take the
trade. Didn't take it. Now, I avoided a
win, so the trade actually played out
perfectly. NZD/USD gave me the perfect
trade setup, the perfect trade
continuation sell and I missed out on
the trade. Now, did that make me feel
some type of way? Did I feel emotional?
Did I get greedy? Did I then go find
another trade setup? No. It just made me
more confident than you can even even
imagine. The fact that I'm actually able
to make 750 grand on two trade setups. I
predicted trades perfectly. I hold the
trade, comes back to break even, goes
back to [music] my take profit. I close
the trade out. I analyze another trade
setup that is another perfect trade
setup and I don't take it is far more
powerful to me than actually executing
the trade. The fact that I have that
self-control to make a lot of money in a
single week and not take the next trade
setup because I'm following my trading
plan, I respect myself so much more for
that and I makes me so much more
confident in my trading that I'm able to
have that self-control and I feel like
that should be far more impressive to
people than the money that I made
because, you know, I can get lucky in
them trades and predicting the market
and I just, you know, catch the move,
right? Whatever.
Cuz of whatever reason you want to call
it. But me controlling myself after
making all that money and having another
opportunity is far more impressive not
clicking that button than clicking that
button because a lot of people out there
they fail because they click that button
too often and they don't know how to
have that self-control. So, that was
honestly probably one of the the
highlights personally out of this whole
entire challenge. The fact that I did
not take that next trade setup because
that could have made me lose probably
half of the profits that I made on the
biggest [music] trade.
But
I didn't make the money, but I also
didn't lose anything. All right, ladies
and gentlemen, we are back after
breaking the record of making 750,000.
Let me get you guys the exact number on
how much money I just made.
So, this is an update a couple hours
later, you know, editor, please pop the
up the Instagram reel of me closing out
the trade live.
We closed out for a total of 730,000.
We have officially withdrawn half a
million dollars from our 750,000
record day or week if you want to call
it. And I mean, I'm just going to let
the markets speak for themselves, right?
So, EUR/USD we closed out this trade
here like a [__]
[__] bro. This literally continued to
drop to the downside where I could have
made double of what I had originally
closed out at this point. All right, so
we're back. So, I guess the computer
starts like overheating and starts
lagging, right? But okay, we're here.
So, basically EUR/USD had a beautiful
continuation push to the downside. As
you can tell, we had a massive push to
the downside after having this beautiful
break of this lower low, creating a new
lower low. This is a perfect lower high,
left head, right shoulder, rejection
from the area of interest. Literally
everything that we would want to see
from the trade. Beautiful weekly bearish
engulfing after these eight weeks of
just consolidation, nine weeks of
consolidation. And now it's just a very
easy play. We continue selling this
trade to the downside. I have the
perfect would have had the perfect entry
to pretty much swing this for the next
two weeks.
But I'm just not that guy right now. I'm
not going to lie, I'm not that guy to be
entering those type of trades. And I
just decided to close my trade out
there.
NZD/USD, I did not manage to catch this
trade. As you guys can tell, this
happened literally perfectly. I was
waiting for this trade to give me that
bearish rejection candlestick. Was a bit
too low on the retracement. I was just
being way too picky. And on this
pickiness, I literally decided like I I
just missed out on this whole entire
move. But this is another perfect
example of the markets playing out to
perfection. This is Picasso. This is
artwork. This is just how the market
should move. Break, retest of the area
of interest, rejection, engulfing, sell.
Like that's it. That's just how the
market should move. This is how we have
been able to catch these trades week
after week after week. So, this market
played out perfectly. GBP/CHF, like I
said, massive countertrend trade,
massive high-risk trade. I did not
execute this trade and we avoided this
loss by simply just sticking to the
trades that make the most sense. Even
the ones like these that look the best,
they're still high risk at the end of
the day. And you know, it doesn't really
make sense to take a trade if it's a
high risk. Yes, it has all the other
possible confluences at the lowest point
ever. Blah blah blah blah blah blah
blah. Still a high risk trade, right?
Next we have AUD/USD, which we were
completely wrong about this trade. And
obviously we were right pretty much
about every other single market. And
this did not have the move to the
upside. And last but not least, I
believe it was EUR/GBP, which we had the
countertrend trade here. And then we had
the reaction from this level exactly how
I anticipated. So,
we are pretty much, I don't know, what
what do you want to call it? A
three for seven, four for seven. All you
really need is just one. You need to
catch one or two of these a week and
that's all you need. And this is what I
do every single week with my students
inside of my community. I literally
share with them every single one of
these trades live as they're happening.
And I'm like, "Yo, guys, Sunday." So,
Sunday swings, I get on a call. I'm
like, "Yo, we're going to be interested
in this, this, this.
This is why this is why we're not going
to be interested in this." And then
after I do like one-on-one calls with my
students and then I get to like further
break down trades that they're taking in
the past, mistakes that they do. I
literally review the trades. So, if you
guys want to know more about this, hit
the link in the description down below
because it's something that I do every
single week and I only do with a very
close group of people because it's not
something that I I do with everybody cuz
it's simply I'm I'm one person and I can
only work with a certain amount of
people. So, I I would try my best to
make it the best quality possible and it
not be something that I just let anybody
in. So, if you guys want to know more
about that, link in the description.
Broker that I use in the link in the
description down below. And if at this
point in the video you are not
subscribed to the channel to this
channel, which is just strictly about
trading, all I can say is you're missing
out. Hit that subscribe button. Every
single week I'm dropping live bangers
just like this one where I am giving you
my whole entire thought process, my
whole entire rundown of the exact trades
that I'm entering, why I'm entering it,
how I'm entering it, the full breakdown.
And I think this is very educational. I
think this is very real, raw, and how I
trade while I'm traveling, how I trade
when I break records like these this one
that I just broke right now, or how I
just trade when I'm in my regular normal
routine. I've been here in Dubai for
two weeks now. I'll probably be here for
another week, maybe two weeks, and then
head back to Miami cuz honestly the
trading here is pretty ridiculous. And
I'm actually able to trade better. My my
my my trading time zone is so much
better because I don't have to wake up
for London session. I just stay up. Or
maybe I go back to Miami and I just stay
with this sleep schedule, which is
pretty crazy cuz right now it is 1:00 in
the afternoon and it's 5:00 in the
morning in Miami time. So, and the rest
of the week pretty much consisted of us
just living life in Dubai. I think this
is the first actual trip where I
genuinely had a lot of fun off camera,
right? Usually I record the majority of
the stuff that I'm living. But for the
first time ever, I didn't even think
about that. I just genuinely enjoyed
having a great time with my guys, with
with you guys that saw me out there at
the Forex Expo. I had a lot of
conversation with you guys. Like I I
finally did a crazy record week and I
actually enjoyed it without having to do
anything for content. I just did it to
actually have fun. And we captured some
moments. And next week we're actually
going to upload the full week in the
life of Dubai, which I think it's going
to be one of my favorite videos that I
have ever recorded just because we're
just having a buck ton of fun. And
whatever can come out comes out,
whatever can come out can't come out.
[music] So, if you guys want to see that
video, make sure you hit that subscribe
button, turn the notifications on so you
guys can see that video as soon as it
comes live. But this week is not an
anomaly. It might be an anomaly because
of the amount of money that I made this
week because it's a record number. But I
predict these markets every single week.
And I'm talking about every single week.
I'm literally sharing the full breakdown
of why I'm interested in entering a
trade and why I'm not interested in
entering other trades. I do this live
with my students every single Sunday
where my students are literally
following the exact same trades that I
am taking. Cuz a lot of traders when
they join my community, they might be
lost because they don't know how to
execute a strategy or they might not
even know how to analyze the markets.
That's why I do what I like to call the
famous Sunday swings where I set up
every single Sunday the perfect markets
for the week ahead. So, not only are you
executing the strategy perfectly, but
you're also doing it with me. So, you
know what markets to focus on and what
markets to not focus on. And then you
get educated live on the markets every
single week. And I review your trades if
you do them right or if you do them
wrong and what mistakes you make. So, if
you guys want to know more about how to
be part of my community and be part of
these calls, just click the link in the
description down below. Honestly, this
is only something that I am doing now
for the next 6 to 12 months where I'm
going to be making sure that you're
executing the right trades with my
strategy where I get to review it and
see if it makes sense for you. Sadly, my
community is no longer open to
everybody. It is now off of the
application basis only cuz it takes a
lot of my time to make sure that you're
trading just like me. Like if I'm going
to walk you by the hand and make sure
that you're following the trading
strategy perfectly, I got to do that
with the right people. Takes a lot of my
time and I want to make sure I'm helping
the right people because it sharpens me
as a trader if I am teaching you
correctly and if you're actually paying
attention. And if you even qualified or
even at the right moment to actually
learn the strategy. So, all I can say is
hit that like and subscribe button. Want
to join the community, click the link
down below. And this record-breaking
week might get broken once again. And
we're [music] going to show the people
once again how we do it every single
week. So, all I can say is get ready
because I am. See you guys in the next
video and set and forget.